thevpn.guru 2019-02-26

# Privacy Policy - The VPN Guru

**TheVPN.guru** acknowledges the importance of its visitors’ privacy. Our privacy policy outlines the what information we collect, why we collect it, and how we use such information.

**TheVPN.guru** might have to revise this Privacy Policy in the future in order comply with any applicable European regulations. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page, so please check back periodically. Prior versions of this Privacy Policy are kept in our archive for revision purposes.

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://thevpn.guru.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Types of Information

When you visit the Website **theVPN.guru** , we may collect data such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, and browser type. You are hereby notified that we collect and store this information in the aggregate only and we do not combine this information with other personal data collected from you. In connection with your activity on our web server, we may collect your IP address, time and date of request, page requested, user agent, referrer and cookie values sent or received.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Cookies

**TheVPN.guru** uses cookies to store and collect information about your usage of the site in order to enhance your online experience and to help us improve the quality of our services.

When you access **theVPN.guru** , your computer automatically sends us information such as the URL on our site you have visited, your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Links

**TheVPN.guru** posts and pages may contain hypertext links to other sites and other third parties. By clicking on these links, you are leaving **theVPN.guru** website. **TheVPN.guru** has no control whatsoever over the information collected by any third party after you leave our website. Therefore, we highly recommend that you to read the privacy policies of these respective websites.

The data collection and usage practices of any third party linked to **theVPN.guru** are not covered by this Privacy Policy. **TheVPN.guru** assumes no liability nor responsibility for any practices of these third party websites, including their privacy practices or content, under any circumstances.

### Analytics

When someone visits  **https://thevpn.guru**  we use a third-party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be upfront about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## How to contact us

For further inquiries or suggestions, you can contact us by sending an email to legal@thevpn.guru
